A Guide to the Boush family papers, 1855-2012
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Boush family papers, 1855-2012
The Library of Virginia
51108
.225 cu. ft. (1 box)
Boush family
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Helen Elizabeth McLeod and John Goodenow Tyler, III, of Norfolk.
Biographical Information
The Boush family resided in Princess Anne County, Norfolk, and Virginia Beach, Virginia.
Scope and Content
Papers, 1855-2012, of the Boush family of Norfolk and Virginia Beach, Virginia containing a Boush family genealogy; portraits and photographs of the Boush family; clipping and card for Boy Scout Troop 62 (Oceana); power of attorney from Eileen Boush Davis to Eileen Davis Vernon; papers relating to the 1762 Samuel Boush map of Norfolk; appraisal of the artwork owned by Eileen Davis; 1862 sketch of Norfolk from Harper's Weekly; Ye Hysterical Historie of Norfolk Towne by Frank Wing; and transcript of letter, 5 February 1855, from Richard Wagner to a friend and related papers.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
Samuel Boush's plan for Norfolk, 1762 (LVA map call number G3884.N6 1762.N5).
Contents List
- Boush family papers, 1855-2012., Extent: .225 cu. ft. (1 box)
  - Boush family genealogy, undated. (Folder 1)
  - Portraits and photographs, undated. (Folder 2)
  - Boy Scout Troop 62, Oceana, 1938, undated. (Folder 3)
  - Power of attorney, Eileen Boush Davis to Eileen Davis Vernon, 23 December 2008. (Folder 4)
  - Papers relating to Samuel Boush map (1762) (map is located in the map collection, call number G3884.N6 1762.N5), 1945-2012. (Folder 5)
  - Art appraisals (Davis and Vernon), 2011. (Folder 6)
  - City of Norfolk scene from Harper's Weekly, 19 April 1862. (Folder 7)
  - Ye Hysterical Historie of Norfolk Towne by Frank Wing, 1931. (Folder 8)
  - Richard Wagner letter and related correspondence, 1855, 1973-1974, 1986. (Folder 9)